So in the last lesson we talked about how to describe things clearly right.
所以在上一课我们讲了如何把事情描述清楚正确。
In this lesson we're going to also focus on something that's very very important to know how to do to
在本课中，我们还将关注一些非常重要的事情，知道如何去做
know how to use if you want to be able to speak English.
如果您想能够说英语，就知道如何使用。
Well if you feel very very comfortable with different verb tenses which is what we're going to talk
好吧，如果你对不同的动词时态感到非常舒服，这就是我们要说的
about in this lesson you can skip this one and go to the next.
关于在本课中，您可以跳过这一课并转到下一课。
But if you don't feel totally confident then you really need to watch this lesson very carefully.
但是，如果您不完全有信心，那么您真的需要非常仔细地观看这一课。
We do this one and the last lesson because it's so important to have these things first before we go
我们做这节课和最后一节课，因为在我们走之前先掌握这些东西非常重要
on to some of the more fun stuff like inviting people to do things or hanging out at a coffee shop or
一些更有趣的事情，比如邀请人们做事或在咖啡店闲逛或
ordering stuff.
订购东西。
That's a lot more maybe fun and interesting but we really need to make sure we have the what I would
这可能更有趣和有趣，但我们真的需要确保我们拥有我想要的
call fundamentals.
叫基本面。
Oh I don't even have room fundamentals down.
哦，我什至没有房间基础。
This should be done.
应该这样做。
Fundamentals down.
基本面下降。
Before we get into that other stuff.
在我们进入其他内容之前。
So a tense what is that what is what is a verb tense.
所以一个时态what is that what 是动词时态。
Well in English when you're saying things that happen you're talking about what happened and you need
英语很好，当你说发生的事情时，你在谈论发生的事情，你需要
to say when it happened yesterday tomorrow today.
说昨天明天今天什么时候发生的。
Now we use different verb tenses to basically say when the action happen we have to change verbs.
现在我们使用不同的动词时态基本上说当动作发生时我们必须改变动词。
I'm sure you know this.
我相信你知道这一点。
We have to change verbs according to when things happen so that they agree with each other.
我们必须根据事情发生的时间来改变动词，以使它们彼此一致。
Right.
正确的。
And this can be a little confusing.
这可能有点令人困惑。
Sometimes it's simple sometimes it's not.
有时它很简单，有时它不是。
We're going to go through these and I'm going to give you examples examples are the best way to learn
我们将通过这些，我将为您提供示例示例是最好的学习方式
how to use verb tenses because knowing these names.
如何使用动词时态，因为知道这些名字。
Simple right past simple tense progressive tense.
简单对过去简单时进行时。
Knowing these names is not that important.
知道这些名字并不重要。
If you don't learn the names of grammar things that's fine because you're not an English teacher right.
如果您不学习语法的名称，那很好，因为您不是英语老师。
I need to know the names of different kinds of grammar but nobody else does.
我需要知道不同类型语法的名称，但没有人知道。
So don't worry about that so much focus on the examples and try to get the feeling for them.
所以不要担心过多地关注这些例子，试着去感受它们。
And then I'll give you some practice to do so that you can actually understand hopefully deeply how
然后我会给你一些练习，这样你就可以真正深入地理解如何
to use different verb tenses and it can become I hope a habit for you so that when you're speaking you
使用不同的动词时态，我希望它可以成为你的习惯，这样当你说话时
don't have to think about it.
不必考虑。
OK.
好的。
That is the goal that you can use these naturally.
那是您可以自然地使用它们的目标。
You don't need to think.
你不需要思考。
So let's get started.
所以让我们开始吧。